ADAPTED FROM DEMON KING
OF JINJIANG LITERATURE CITY
ORIGINAL WORK BY JIULU FEIXIANG
This music is what I've been waiting for.
What music?
Why can't I hear it?
This music…
I've never heard
this music before,
but it seems that I've listened to it
a million times.
Well…
Do you know the player?
No.
I don't know who the player is.
It's bustling outside.
Although I'm not going,
you don't need to stay here.
Go and have fun.
Thank you, my lady.
I'll be right back.
Jieli.
What's wrong?
Where is Orchid?
She's missing.
Look for her.
- Yes.
Forget it.
It's too troublesome.
I'll move away all the people
on the street.
- No.
- My lord.
My lord.
We've agreed that
we don't use magic powers in Lucheng.
My lord, calm down.
It may disturb the fate of Lady Chidi.
You can't do that.
My lord.
Although Orchid's magical power is weak,
it's more than enough for her
to deal with the mortals in Yunmeng Lake.
I'll go and look for her now.
If she is in any danger,
I will throw you both
into the Oblivion River.
Yes.
Let's go.
She is heartbroken
and wants to end her life.
Then she meets her beloved
who understands her well.
If my guess is right,
the former God of War will be
at Flying Immortal Pavilion tonight.
She will meet Lord Changheng
and fall in love at first sight.
I have to keep watch.
I can't let Big Blockhead disturb them.
Xie Wanqing.
That's the Flying Immortal Pavilion.
It's time.
My lord.
Dongfang Qingcang appeared in Lucheng.
I'm afraid
he will disturb
the God of War's tribulation.
What Dongfang Qingcang aims to do
is to take my master's primordial spirit
and unlock 100,000 soldiers
of the Moon Tribe.
So before the hardship is completed,
or before the wedding night
during the Flower Festival,
he won't take any action.
For over 30,000 years,
I've been guarding her
to avoid any problems
during her tribulations.
I finally found the Goddess of Xishan.
This is also the last tribulation
of my master.
So,
you must be careful
and make sure everything goes well.
After this life,
my master can go back with me.
Yes, my lord.
I have no regrets.
"The night of the Lantern Festival."
"Meeting her beloved."
She plans to end her life.
Her beloved will stop her.
But why hasn't her beloved
shown up yet?
Have a look.
- Stop!
- Get out of the way!
- Over there!
Stop!
- Don't run!
- Stop!
- Don't run.
- Here.
Move!
- Don't run!
- Stop!
FLYING IMMORTAL PAVILION
Where are you going?
Wait.
We are on familiar terms with each other.
Why do you have to do this?
- Give me the jade.
- Hand it over!
No.
I was born with this jade.
I can't give it to you.
How about this?
When my father calms down,
I'll pay you double.
All right?
- I don't care who you are.
- Take it!
- You dare to play tricks in our casino?
- No!
- You have to suffer a lot.
- I can't give it to you.
- Mr. Xiao.
- I have to give it to my destined lover!
- You don't have to suffer this for a jade.
Give it to me.
How dare you bite me?
- Beat him!
Stop!
It's perfectly justified to pay the debt.
Where did this wild girl come from?
You'd better mind your own business.
Leave!
Let him go!
Otherwise, don't blame me
for being rude to you.
She's a heroine.
What? Want to show off your bravery?
Attack!
Go!
Stop!
Within the three realms,
you, as a woman,
cannot kill me.
Is it you?
We…
Have we met before?
Never.
The music…
Was the music just now
from you?
What music?
It's you.
It must be you.
Why did I feel hate,
respect,
and concern
at the same time
when I saw you?
It's like I've been entangled with you
for ages.
I think I was waiting for you.
You're drunk.
I'm drunk?
Look at this muddy world.
Everyone is drunk.
I'm just dreaming.
At this moment,
I should wake up from my dream.
You can't die.
We met in our previous life.
Who are you?
How could this happen?
Where is her beloved?
He should have appeared.
Are you all right?
Have we
met before?
No.
You must have mistaken me
for someone else.
Since you are fine, I shall take my leave.
No, I can't be wrong.
- I…
- No.
Last month,
we met at the mansion of Duke Zhongyi.
At that time,
his wife was training
with female generals.
You knocked off my hair bun.
What? What female generals?
I've never heard of it.
How forgetful I am!
It's rare to see
such a beautiful technique.
You must be the legitimate heir
of the magician of Liuyun Theatre.
Half a month ago,
I watched your performance.
Sir, you must be mistaken.
We've never seen each other in this life.
I remember now.
There is a beautiful fairy in my dream.
She looks very similar to you.
You and I
must have a relationship in heaven.
Heroine, wait.
I haven't asked your name yet.
Where do you live? What's your name?
Heroine.
- Heroine.
- It's almost midnight.
Why is the lord still wandering here?
Why isn't he going to meet Xie Wanqing?
After the night of the Lantern Festival,
the fate will be changed.
I was worried about you
and looked for you everywhere.
But you're here
to meet Changheng secretly.
Changheng?
Isn't Lord Changheng at Shuiyuntian?
You got the wrong person.
You are still lying.
Do you really think I am a child
who will be fooled by your tricks?
At the Flying Immortal Pavilion,
I found that Changheng is also
experiencing tribulations.
Everything you said and did
was just covering up for Changheng.
Even so,
I would rather believe it when you said
the Bone Orchid I gave you is priceless.
But you…
Yes.
I lied to you.
What about you?
Why did you come to Lucheng?
You said you came to hang around with me.
But you came for the primordial spirit
of the God of War, right?
How did you know?
Jieli told you?
She didn't say anything.
I guessed it according to the fate poem.
How smart you are,
the head disciple of the Arbiter!
Since you are so good at guessing,
did you know
about Changheng's hardship long ago?
I…
Good. Very good.
No wonder you came to Lucheng
without permission
and claimed that
you wanted to hang with me.
So you had a plan.
I didn't.
I knew it not long ago.
This is a rare opportunity.
I'm going to kill Changheng now
and get rid of a big trouble
for Cangyan Sea.
No. You can't kill him.
Lord Changheng is the beloved!
What did you say?
Xiao Run was betrothed
to Xie Wanqing before birth
and offered a lot of money to propose.
They will show up
at Flying Immortal Pavilion tonight.
There must be no mistake.
If you kill him on impulse,
Xie Wanqing's fate will change too.
It's because of you.
What do you mean?
If Changheng
is the beloved in the poem as you said,
then he didn't show up on time
because he wasted time
pushing and pulling with you
and thus changed his fate.
If I hadn't stopped Xie Wanqing,
she would have already died.
What?
You stopped Xie Wanqing?
Why are you so nosy?
It's not her fate.
If I didn't stop her and let her die,
there would be no turning back.
This is bad.
They've missed the destined time.
They should have fallen in love tonight,
but they didn't meet each other.
If things don't happen
according to the fate poem,
the two of them will fail
in the tribulation…
- and their primordial spirits will perish.
- Their primordial spirits will perish.
EVERLASTING ORCHID
Xiao Run.
After coming home today,
you look as if you've lost your soul.
You've been staring at the blank paper
for the whole night.
You don't understand.
If I don't draw when I am fully prepared,
I will offend that heroine.
Xiao Run.
It's 1:30 a.m.
After school tomorrow,
you need to visit Lady Wanqing
at the Flying Immortal Pavilion.
Rest early.
I won't go there tomorrow.
It's not Lady Wanqing.
I was wrong.
That heroine
is the actual fairy in my dream.
Another girl?
What do you mean?
It's different this time.
I can feel
that the heroine is the fairy in my dream.
I was born with this jade.
I was born for her.
Then…
Xiao Run, take your time.
Who are you?
You are Fairy Danyin.
Are you a thief?
Guards!
Help!
- Help!
- Qu Shui!
Thief!
Qu Shui!
Who dares to break into Xiao's Mansion?
I came to Lucheng.
You also came to Lucheng.
You and I are destined to meet.
How…
You bandit, I'll beat you!
Stop!
Let him go!
Sir, you must be mistaken.
There is a beautiful fairy in my dream.
She looks very similar to you.
You and I
must have a relationship in heaven.
Why isn't he back yet?
So? Did it go well?
It's easy to erase
a mortal's memory.
No.
The problem is not fully solved yet.
Even if Xiao Run's memory
of meeting me was erased,
he still hasn't met Xie Wanqing.
You…
Why are you looking at me?
Orchid, you fix Destiny Books.
No one knows about tribulations
better than you.
Hurry up and find a way!
Let me get it straight.
On the night of the Lantern Festival,
the God of War Changheng or Xiao Run,
was destined to meet Lady Chidi,
Xie Wanqing,
at the Flying Immortal Pavilion
and save Xie Wanqing
who would fall off the building.
They'd fall in love with each other.
But because Big Blockhead and I
were careless,
they missed each other.
Because of you two,
their fates
deviated from the…
Fate poem.
Yes. Fate poem.
If they didn't meet,
they wouldn't be in love.
If they aren't in love,
they won't get married.
If so,
Xie Wanqing won't be able
to be killed by Xiao Run
on the wedding night.
I have a question.
Since Changheng wanted to marry her,
why would he kill her?
I'm also curious about this.
Lord Changheng is a person
who values love and loyalty.
Why would he kill Xie Wanqing?
Yes.
Is there someone who values
love and loyalty in the Fairy Realm?
This is the first time I've ever known it.
My lord, Changheng is a mortal now.
A mortal is able to value love
and loyalty.
Don't stray from the point.
This is not important.
Anyway, if nothing in the fate poem
happens now,
then the hardship experience
of Changheng and Lady Chidi
will be a failure.
Their primordial spirits
will vanish.
Am I right?
Accidents before the tribulation
are not terrible.
What's important
is the tribulation experience.
If they are destined to love each other,
how they meet doesn't matter.
I know!
I see!
You understand too?
- No.
- Then why did you say that?
I was trying to lighten the atmosphere.
So what do you know now?
Think about it.
As long as they get married
during the Flower Festival,
the fate poem will still come true
and the tribulation will succeed.
So our main task now
is to make them fall in love before that.
But they already missed
the best opportunity.
How can we make them fall in love?
You don't understand.
Xiao Run and Xie Wanqing
are a match made in heaven.
This little setback can't tear them apart.
Look.
Xiao Run doesn't value
fame and fortune at all.
He refuses to follow
his family's arrangement.
Xie Wanqing doesn't value
wealth and splendor.
She refuses to care about worldly taste.
They don't do anything against their will.
Aren't they a perfect match?
So now, as long as they meet,
fate will naturally lead them
to fall in love at first sight.
There's no time to lose.
I'll go find Xiao Run
and ask him to meet Xie Wanqing.
Don't go.
I went to erase Xiao Run's memory
to avoid more trouble.
If you go there rashly,
it would be in vain.
Exactly.
The relations between men and women
should develop naturally.
Orchid, it's not appropriate for you
to go find Xiao Run.
Exactly.
Since you want to be a mortal,
you must follow the rules of mortals.
How about letting Moon Supreme
and Shangque get close to Xiao Run?
As for Xie Wanqing,
Orchid and I will take charge of her.
After getting along with them,
we'll find a way to let them meet.
What do you think? Any problem?
- No.
- We can't do this.
Why?
You're afraid I'll take Changheng's life,
aren't you?
You underestimate me.
He's a mortal now.
He has no power.
If I kill him,
I'm not different from those hypocrites
in the Fairy Realm.
Are you sure you won't hurt him?
The tribulation is more important now.
I don't have time to waste energy
in the Mortal World.
Let's do it then.
Wait. I still don't understand.
- I still have questions.
- Good. Dismissed.
Wait, listen to me.
Let's go.
- Wait.
- Come on.
I haven't finished yet.
Wait.
I have something to tell you. Sit down.
What do you want to say?
You are awake, my lady?
Are you feeling unwell?
You were drunk on the rooftop last night.
If you caught a cold,
it would be my fault.
Last night, I saw someone
on the rooftop.
He was very mysterious.
He came in the moonlight.
Except for me,
no one went to the rooftop last night.
You must've been drunk.
You had a dream.
Impossible.
I remember it clearly.
That person…
Could it be
really a dream?
My lady, you must have been wanting
to find a perfect husband.
That's why you had that dream.
INVITATION
What is this?
SPRING BANQUET
Gosh, I forgot to tell you.
This is the invitation sent by Lady Cui
from Shiyu Pavilion
to invite you to the Spring Banquet
ten days from today.
Those royal descendants
and noble ladies of noble families
always recite poems
and play grass games during the banquet.
It happens every year.
I'm tired of it.
Decline it for me.
Yes.
Wait.
Get the best gardener in Lucheng for me.
Yes.
Xiao Run!
Why are we sleeping in the yard?
Right.
Last night,
there was a thief.
I was so scared that I…
And then?
I passed out.
Xiao Run, are you all right?
I'm fine.
But I feel as if
I forgot something important.
Xiao Run.
Don't scare me.
Did you hurt your brain
when you fought against the thief?
Or
did you come across ghosts?
In broad daylight,
it's impossible to see ghosts.
What time is it now?
It should be
around 7:00 a.m. now.
Hurry! Pack up!
If my old man knows I missed school,
I will be skinned!
Move!
Xiao Run.
Xiao Run, hurry up! It's late.
What are you doing?
Where is this painting from?
You painted it yourself yesterday.
Did you forget?
We are really late!
This must be drawn in my dream.
The woman in the painting
must be the fairy in my dream.
Qu Shui!
I know everything.
Know what?
I know what she looks like.
I finally know.
Qu Shui, I finally know!
Dark Golden Glory is the best
among peonies.
It's the most delicate.
Since the day I planted it,
I've been taking care of it every day.
I've invited countless gardeners,
but no one can make it bloom.
Lady Orchid,
you are an excellent gardener.
Now it has buds.
Don't worry.
I'll make sure it blooms
before the Spring Banquet.
I heard that Lady Orchid is renowned
as Jinling's head of flower fairies.
It shows that the rumor is true.
I'm flattered.
I've heard that Jinling
is full of talented people.
Lady Orchid, don't be modest.
I'm just an ordinary person.
I accepted your invitation
for a personal reason.
If I can accompany you
to the Spring Banquet,
maybe I can meet a fated person.
A young gentleman will be attracted
to beautiful ladies.
If you can meet someone you like,
it will be good.
Do you have someone
in your heart?
Maybe my destined one
is the moon in the sky.
The moon in the sky is bright and clear,
and it always hangs in the sky.
It's untouchable.
Xie Wanqing's dream lover
really is Lord Changheng.
"It is the year of Guichou.
On one of those late spring days,
we gather at the Orchid Pavilion
to dispel bad luck
and pray for good fortune.
The attendees of the gathering…"
Xiao Run, the teacher is coming.
This is…
It's you.
You are
the rich merchant
who bought the Night Stream Building!
It's him.
- It's him?
- So this is him.
He bought the Night Stream Building?
Silence!
This is Mr. Dongfang.
He will be your classmate from now on.
I haven't finished yet.
What else can you say?
Let the class begin.
Look at his vibe.
So impressive.
Yes.
All right.
Let's continue to review.
Mr. Dongfang.
You really have an impressive presence.
Nice to meet you.
My name is widely known
because of my money.
These mortals
are so dull.
Mr. Dongfang,
you're really extraordinary.
Stop whispering!
You two, get out!
Mr. Dongfang, I'm talking to you.
- How dare you talk to me like that?
- Calm down, sir.
RECTIFICATION, CULTIVATION,
CONTEMPLATION, DILIGENCE
Mr. Dongfang.
There is a Cuju match
in the west of the city.
Why don't we go and have a look?
School is not over yet.
Someone must be guarding the front gate.
I have a good plan.
You two stay here.
Let's go!
Go!
Mr. Dongfang, hurry up! No one is here.
Mr. Dongfang!
Mr. Dongfang, hurry up!
- Mr. Dongfang!
- I'm coming.
Hurry up.
Come on.
Be careful.
I can't believe
I just crawled through a dog hole
with Changheng hand in hand.
What did you say?
- Nothing.
- Who is sneaking around?
Let's go.
Mr. Xiao.
It's you again.
Master.
It's almost lunchtime.
Have you eaten?
Mr. Xiao.
You've been idling about
and fooling around all day long.
You're stubborn.
You don't focus on your studies at all.
Today, you even crawled through
the dog hole.
You've humiliated yourself.
If it weren't for your father's sake,
- I would have told the secretary.
- Forget it.
I should just do as she says.
- And you.
- Master.
Mr. Dongfang just tried to persuade me
not to do this.
He wanted to drag me back, so he…
It has nothing to do with him.
I forced him out.
Let's run!
You are…
not worth being taught!
WENJUN PAVILION
RECTIFICATION, CULTIVATION,
CONTEMPLATION, DILIGENCE
Shangque, where are they?
They were punished to stand,
but disappeared together.
What? Disappeared together?
RECTIFICATION, CULTIVATION,
CONTEMPLATION, DILIGENCE
HONESTY
THREE POINTS
TEAM BLUE, TEAM RED
It's luck that made you win today.
You still won't admit defeat?
- Let's compete another day.
- Let's go.
- Let's go back.
Mr. Dongfang.
That kick just now was amazing.
They were all out of their wits.
Mr. Dongfang!
I didn't expect that
you would be so good at Cuju.
Teach me if you have time.
When I was young, Father and I…
My father and I
often played Cuju together.
He taught me
a lot of techniques.
Your father even taught you to play Cuju?
My old man always tells me
not to be a boy without ambitions.
I should focus on studying
and earning fame.
In my opinion,
I don't care about fame and fortune.
This wooden ball
is the best thing in the world.
That's right!
It's said that it's hard
to find a bosom friend.
I didn't expect that
I could find a confidant today.
Wait.
I have something to tell you. Sit down.
Next time when you meet your friends,
don't always pull a long face.
If you don't know how to answer him,
just smile at him.
Smile again?
Didn't I teach you that
when you made peace with Xunfeng?
Like this.
Do you remember?
Mr. Dongfang.
How did you hurt your hand?
I'm fine.
What are you doing?
It's the medicine I made for knife wounds.
When my father flogged me,
I relied on this to survive.
Don't move.